{"questionArray": [
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(33)\\).", "answer": "37", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 33\nf(33) \u003d (33) + 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(33) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 20\\). Evaluate \\(f(21)\\).", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 21\nf(21) \u003d (21) - 20\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(21) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 3\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "8", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d (5) + 3\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 21\\). Evaluate \\(f(43)\\).", "answer": "22", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 43\nf(43) \u003d (43) - 21\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(43) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 7\\). Evaluate \\(f(37)\\).", "answer": "44", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 37\nf(37) \u003d (37) + 7\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(37) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(25)\\).", "answer": "7", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 25\nf(25) \u003d (25) - 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(25) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 5\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "14", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d (9) + 5\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 19\\). Evaluate \\(f(47)\\).", "answer": "28", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 47\nf(47) \u003d (47) - 19\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(47) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 9\\). Evaluate \\(f(7)\\).", "answer": "-2", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 7\nf(7) \u003d (7) - 9\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 17\\). Evaluate \\(f(45)\\).", "answer": "62", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 45\nf(45) \u003d (45) + 17\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(45) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(32)\\).", "answer": "22", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 32\nf(32) \u003d (32) - 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(32) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(20)\\).", "answer": "36", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 20\nf(20) \u003d (20) + 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(20) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 7\\). Evaluate \\(f(11)\\).", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 11\nf(11) \u003d (11) - 7\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(11) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 19\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d (1) + 19\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(35)\\).", "answer": "27", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 35\nf(35) \u003d (35) - 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(35) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(23)\\).", "answer": "41", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 23\nf(23) \u003d (23) + 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(23) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(15)\\).", "answer": "11", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 15\nf(15) \u003d (15) - 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(15) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 21\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "26", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d (5) + 21\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(39)\\).", "answer": "33", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 39\nf(39) \u003d (39) - 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(39) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 20\\). Evaluate \\(f(27)\\).", "answer": "47", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 27\nf(27) \u003d (27) + 20\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(27) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 2\\). Evaluate \\(f(19)\\).", "answer": "17", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 19\nf(19) \u003d (19) - 2\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(19) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 23\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "32", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d (9) + 23\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 3\\). Evaluate \\(f(43)\\).", "answer": "40", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 43\nf(43) \u003d (43) - 3\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(43) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 22\\). Evaluate \\(f(31)\\).", "answer": "53", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 31\nf(31) \u003d (31) + 22\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(31) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(7)\\).", "answer": "25", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 7\nf(7) \u003d (7) + 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 7\\). Evaluate \\(f(44)\\).", "answer": "37", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 44\nf(44) \u003d (44) - 7\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(44) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(31)\\).", "answer": "47", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 31\nf(31) \u003d (31) + 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(31) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(19)\\).", "answer": "11", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 19\nf(19) \u003d (19) - 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(19) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 20\\). Evaluate \\(f(10)\\).", "answer": "30", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 10\nf(10) \u003d (10) + 20\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 5\\). Evaluate \\(f(48)\\).", "answer": "43", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 48\nf(48) \u003d (48) - 5\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(48) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 19\\). Evaluate \\(f(34)\\).", "answer": "53", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 34\nf(34) \u003d (34) + 19\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(34) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(22)\\).", "answer": "16", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 22\nf(22) \u003d (22) - 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(22) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 22\\). Evaluate \\(f(14)\\).", "answer": "36", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 14\nf(14) \u003d (14) + 22\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(14) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 3\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d (4) - 3\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 21\\). Evaluate \\(f(38)\\).", "answer": "59", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 38\nf(38) \u003d (38) + 21\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(38) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(26)\\).", "answer": "22", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 26\nf(26) \u003d (26) - 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(26) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 24\\). Evaluate \\(f(18)\\).", "answer": "42", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 18\nf(18) \u003d (18) + 24\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(18) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x\\). Evaluate \\(f(8)\\).", "answer": "8", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 8\nf(8) \u003d (8)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 23\\). Evaluate \\(f(42)\\).", "answer": "65", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 42\nf(42) \u003d (42) + 23\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(42) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 1\\). Evaluate \\(f(30)\\).", "answer": "29", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 30\nf(30) \u003d (30) - 1\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(30) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 9\\). Evaluate \\(f(41)\\).", "answer": "50", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 41\nf(41) \u003d (41) + 9\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(41) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(29)\\).", "answer": "13", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 29\nf(29) \u003d (29) - 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(29) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(13)\\).", "answer": "21", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 13\nf(13) \u003d (13) + 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(13) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 17\\). Evaluate \\(f(3)\\).", "answer": "-14", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 3\nf(3) \u003d (3) - 17\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 11\\). Evaluate \\(f(45)\\).", "answer": "56", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 45\nf(45) \u003d (45) + 11\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(45) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 14\\). Evaluate \\(f(33)\\).", "answer": "19", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 33\nf(33) \u003d (33) - 14\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(33) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(17)\\).", "answer": "27", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 17\nf(17) \u003d (17) + 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(17) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 15\\). Evaluate \\(f(7)\\).", "answer": "-8", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 7\nf(7) \u003d (7) - 15\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 13\\). Evaluate \\(f(49)\\).", "answer": "62", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 49\nf(49) \u003d (49) + 13\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(49) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 11\\). Evaluate \\(f(37)\\).", "answer": "26", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 37\nf(37) \u003d (37) - 11\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(37) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "-10", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d -10*(1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "-30", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d -6*(5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "7", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d -(-7)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "35", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d 7*(5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "-40", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d -8*(5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "-36", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d -4*(9)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "-3", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d (-3)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "9", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d 9*(1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "-45", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d -5*(9)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "14", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d -2*(-7)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d 3*(1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x\\). Evaluate \\(f(2)\\).", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 2\nf(2) \u003d -6*(2)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d -(-10)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "-18", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d 3*(-6)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "-48", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d 8*(-6)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "-24", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d -4*(6)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "-6", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d (-6)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "-50", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d 5*(-10)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-2)\\).", "answer": "20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -2\nf(-2) \u003d -10*(-2)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d -2*(-10)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-2)\\).", "answer": "-8", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -2\nf(-2) \u003d 4*(-2)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "-42", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d 7*(-6)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x\\). Evaluate \\(f(2)\\).", "answer": "-16", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 2\nf(2) \u003d -8*(2)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x\\). Evaluate \\(f(2)\\).", "answer": "12", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 2\nf(2) \u003d 6*(2)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-2)\\).", "answer": "-18", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -2\nf(-2) \u003d 9*(-2)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "-30", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d -5*(6)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "54", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d 6*(9)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "-63", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d 9*(-7)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "42", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d -6*(-7)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d 2*(5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "-56", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d 8*(-7)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "27", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -9*(-3)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "9", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -3*(-3)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "36", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d 4*(9)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "30", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -10*(-3)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "-7", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d -7*(1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "-1", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d -(1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "-49", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d 7*(-7)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "-8", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d -8*(1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "12", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -4*(-3)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "5", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d (5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "-45", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d -9*(5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "21", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d -3*(-7)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "30", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d 6*(5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "-63", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d -7*(9)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -(-3)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d 2*(1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x - 15\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "-57", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d 6*(-7) - 15\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x - 21\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "-57", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d -6*(6) - 21\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 17\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -1*(-3) + 17\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 1\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "28", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d 3*(9) + 1\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x - 11\\). Evaluate \\(f(8)\\).", "answer": "53", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 8\nf(8) \u003d 8*(8) - 11\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 17\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "11", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d -4*(-7) - 17\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 21\\). Evaluate \\(f(-9)\\).", "answer": "12", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -9\nf(-9) \u003d 1*(-9) + 21\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x + 5\\). Evaluate \\(f(-4)\\).", "answer": "-15", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -4\nf(-4) \u003d 5*(-4) + 5\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x - 7\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "53", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d -10*(-6) - 7\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(-5)\\).", "answer": "38", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -5\nf(-5) \u003d -4*(-5) + 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d 1*(-6) + 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x - 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(-2)\\).", "answer": "-18", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -2\nf(-2) \u003d 5*(-2) - 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x - 20\\). Evaluate \\(f(-4)\\).", "answer": "20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -4\nf(-4) \u003d -10*(-4) - 20\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 22\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d -2*(1) + 22\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 12\\). Evaluate \\(f(0)\\).", "answer": "12", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 0\nf(0) \u003d 3*(0) + 12\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(0) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "24", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d 7*(4) - 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(3)\\).", "answer": "-40", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 3\nf(3) \u003d -8*(3) - 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-1)\\).", "answer": "-9", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -1\nf(-1) \u003d 9*(-1)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 12\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -5*(-3) - 12\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x - 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(2)\\).", "answer": "-14", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 2\nf(2) \u003d 2*(2) - 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x + 20\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "28", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d 8*(1) + 20\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x + 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "-41", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d -9*(5) + 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "-20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d -3*(4) - 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x + 3\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d 7*(1) + 3\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 9\\). Evaluate \\(f(-8)\\).", "answer": "55", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -8\nf(-8) \u003d -8*(-8) - 9\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x - 23\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "-39", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d -4*(4) - 23\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 15\\). Evaluate \\(f(2)\\).", "answer": "17", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 2\nf(2) \u003d 1*(2) + 15\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x + 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(8)\\).", "answer": "78", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 8\nf(8) \u003d 9*(8) + 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "-36", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d -5*(6) - 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x - 19\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d -2*(-10) - 19\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 19\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "55", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d 4*(9) + 19\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x + 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "64", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d -9*(-6) + 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 2\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "19", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d -3*(-7) - 2\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 22\\). Evaluate \\(f(-5)\\).", "answer": "-8", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -5\nf(-5) \u003d 6*(-5) + 22\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x + 14\\). Evaluate \\(f(0)\\).", "answer": "14", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 0\nf(0) \u003d -6*(0) + 14\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(0) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x + 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(-1)\\).", "answer": "5", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -1\nf(-1) \u003d -1*(-1) + 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x - 12\\). Evaluate \\(f(-9)\\).", "answer": "-30", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -9\nf(-9) \u003d 2*(-9) - 12\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x - 24\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "-104", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d 8*(-10) - 24\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x + 2\\). Evaluate \\(f(3)\\).", "answer": "-19", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 3\nf(3) \u003d -7*(3) + 2\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "-11", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d -1*(1) - 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 24\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d 2*(-7) + 24\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 8x + 14\\). Evaluate \\(f(-8)\\).", "answer": "-50", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -8\nf(-8) \u003d 8*(-8) + 14\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "18", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -4*(-3) + 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x - 7\\). Evaluate \\(f(-4)\\).", "answer": "-11", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -4\nf(-4) \u003d 1*(-4) - 7\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x - 20\\). Evaluate \\(f(0)\\).", "answer": "-20", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 0\nf(0) \u003d 4*(0) - 20\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(0) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(-2)\\).", "answer": "38", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -2\nf(-2) \u003d -10*(-2) + 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 9\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d -2*(4) + 9\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x - 3\\). Evaluate \\(f(2)\\).", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 2\nf(2) \u003d 3*(2) - 3\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 17\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "25", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d 7*(6) - 17\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x + 21\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "-19", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d -8*(5) + 21\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x + 1\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "46", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d 5*(9) + 1\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x - 13\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "-4", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d 9*(1) - 13\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x - 25\\). Evaluate \\(f(-1)\\).", "answer": "-19", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -1\nf(-1) \u003d -6*(-1) - 25\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x - 14\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "31", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d 5*(9) - 14\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 24\\). Evaluate \\(f(7)\\).", "answer": "-46", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 7\nf(7) \u003d -10*(7) + 24\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -7x + 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(-8)\\).", "answer": "64", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -8\nf(-8) \u003d -7*(-8) + 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d -1*(-10) - 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(-5)\\).", "answer": "-45", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -5\nf(-5) \u003d 7*(-5) - 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 22\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "26", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d -8*(-6) - 22\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 12\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "-12", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d -4*(6) + 12\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "5", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d 1*(5)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x - 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "-96", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d 9*(-10) - 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -6x - 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(8)\\).", "answer": "-66", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 8\nf(8) \u003d -6*(8) - 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(-8)\\).", "answer": "32", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -8\nf(-8) \u003d -2*(-8) + 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 3x + 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(-9)\\).", "answer": "-21", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -9\nf(-9) \u003d 3*(-9) + 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x - 2\\). Evaluate \\(f(-4)\\).", "answer": "34", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -4\nf(-4) \u003d -9*(-4) - 2\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 14\\). Evaluate \\(f(-5)\\).", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -5\nf(-5) \u003d -3*(-5) - 14\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(-2)\\).", "answer": "-2", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -2\nf(-2) \u003d 6*(-2) + 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x + 24\\). Evaluate \\(f(-3)\\).", "answer": "54", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -3\nf(-3) \u003d -10*(-3) + 24\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 12\\). Evaluate \\(f(-5)\\).", "answer": "32", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -5\nf(-5) \u003d -4*(-5) + 12\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -x - 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(7)\\).", "answer": "-11", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 7\nf(7) \u003d -1*(7) - 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 5x - 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "14", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d 5*(6) - 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 22\\). Evaluate \\(f(-9)\\).", "answer": "50", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -9\nf(-9) \u003d -8*(-9) - 22\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(-10)\\).", "answer": "36", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -10\nf(-10) \u003d -2*(-10) + 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-10) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x\\). Evaluate \\(f(-6)\\).", "answer": "-6", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -6\nf(-6) \u003d 1*(-6)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(-7)\\).", "answer": "-59", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -7\nf(-7) \u003d 7*(-7) - 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-7) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -5x - 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(-2)\\).", "answer": "-8", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -2\nf(-2) \u003d -5*(-2) - 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x - 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(-1)\\).", "answer": "-15", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -1\nf(-1) \u003d 9*(-1) - 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -3x - 14\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "-26", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d -3*(4) - 14\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 2x + 24\\). Evaluate \\(f(3)\\).", "answer": "30", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 3\nf(3) \u003d 2*(3) + 24\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 8\\). Evaluate \\(f(-5)\\).", "answer": "-22", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -5\nf(-5) \u003d 6*(-5) + 8\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x - 2\\). Evaluate \\(f(5)\\).", "answer": "-47", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 5\nf(5) \u003d -9*(5) - 2\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d x + 6\\). Evaluate \\(f(3)\\).", "answer": "9", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 3\nf(3) \u003d 1*(3) + 6\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 7x - 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(1)\\).", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 1\nf(1) \u003d 7*(1) - 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x - 19\\). Evaluate \\(f(6)\\).", "answer": "-79", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 6\nf(6) \u003d -10*(6) - 19\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(6) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -4x + 18\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d -4*(4) + 18\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 4x + 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(9)\\).", "answer": "46", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 9\nf(9) \u003d 4*(9) + 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(9) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 9x\\). Evaluate \\(f(8)\\).", "answer": "72", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 8\nf(8) \u003d 9*(8)\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(8) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -8x - 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(0)\\).", "answer": "-16", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 0\nf(0) \u003d -8*(0) - 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(0) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -2x + 22\\). Evaluate \\(f(-1)\\).", "answer": "24", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -1\nf(-1) \u003d -2*(-1) + 22\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-1) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d 6x + 16\\). Evaluate \\(f(4)\\).", "answer": "40", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 4\nf(4) \u003d 6*(4) + 16\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -9x + 4\\). Evaluate \\(f(2)\\).", "answer": "-14", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with 2\nf(2) \u003d -9*(2) + 4\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d"},
  {"question": "\\(f(x) \u003d -10x - 10\\). Evaluate \\(f(-8)\\).", "answer": "70", "explanation": "Replace the x in the function with -8\nf(-8) \u003d -10*(-8) - 10\nSimplify the righthand side", "prompt": "f(-8) \u003d"}
]}